[{
    "question": "`13-2`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-4`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`12-10`",
    "answer": "`2`"
},
{
    "question": "`14-3`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-5`",
    "answer": "`10`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-7`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-2`",
    "answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`20-3`",
    "answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-4`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-7`",
    "answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-4`",
    "answer": "`12`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-6`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-4`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`16-2`",
    "answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-4`",
    "answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`15-7`",
    "answer": "`8`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-5`",
    "answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-5`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`19-13`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-9`",
    "answer": "`8`"
},
{
    "question": "`18-7`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`17-5`",
    "answer": "`12`"
},
{
    "question": "`14-8`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`7-2`",
    "answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-1`",
    "answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-3`",
    "answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-1`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-2`",
    "answer": "`7`"
},
{
    "question": "`4-3`",
    "answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-5`",
    "answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-2`",
    "answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-3`",
    "answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`5-4`",
    "answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-2`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-3`",
    "answer": "`7`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-5`",
    "answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`7-3`",
    "answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-5`",
    "answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-4`",
    "answer": "`5`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-5`",
    "answer": "`3`"
},
{
    "question": "`6-6`",
    "answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-6`",
    "answer": "`4`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-7`",
    "answer": "`1`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-4`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`9-7`",
    "answer": "`2`"
},
{
    "question": "`8-8`",
    "answer": "`0`"
},
{
    "question": "`10-4`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`12-4`",
    "answer": "`8`"
}]